Find your happy place.
Trolls is a family, animation, fantasy film directed by Mike Mitchell.
After the monstrous Bergens invade Troll Village, Princess Poppy, the happiest Troll ever born, and
overly-cautious, curmudgeonly outcast Branch set off on a journey to rescue her friends.
Their mission is full of adventure and mishaps, as this mismatched duo try
to tolerate each other long enough to get the job done.
Poppy (voice), played by Anna Kendrick.
Branch (voice), played by Justin Timberlake.
Bridget (voice), played by Zooey Deschanel.
King Gristle (voice), played by Christopher Mintz-Plasse.
Chef (voice), played by Christine Baranski.
Creek (voice), played by Russell Brand.
Trolls is a 2016 American animated jukebox musical comedy film produced by
DreamWorks Animation, based on the Good Luck Trolls doll line.
The film was directed by Mike Mitchell, written by Jonathan Aibel and Glenn Berger, and stars the voices of
Anna Kendrick, Justin Timberlake, Zooey Deschanel, Russell Brand, James Corden and Gwen Stefani.
The film follows two trolls, Poppy and Branch, who go on a quest to save their
village from destruction by the Bergens, giant creatures who eat Trolls.
Trolls premiered at the BFI London Film Festival on October 8, 2016, and was
theatrically released in the United States on November 4, by 20th Century Fox.
The film grossed $347 million against a $125 million budget.
It received an Academy Award nomination for Best
Original Song for "Can't Stop the Feeling!".
The film launched a franchise, which included two television specials, Trolls Holiday (2017) and
Trolls: Holiday in Harmony (2021), two television series, Trolls: The Beat Goes On!
(2018–2019) and Trolls: TrollsTopia (2020–2022), two sequels, Trolls World Tour
(2020) and Trolls Band Together (2023), and six short films.
The film explores themes of friendship, hunger, villain, musical, based on toy.
The tone is lighthearted.